

Bonnie Lukwiya

Name

luk23bonnie8@gmail.com 🔀

+256753163382

Kampala, Uganda 👂

linkedin.com/in/lukwiya-bonnie-683030189 in

github.com/lukwiya23 🧻

A well-presented and pliable person with solid qualification and a comprehensive skill-set, underpinned by personal work experience in environments demanding self motivation and focused approach. Capable of working under no supervision and willing to assume additional responsibility and to learn, and apply new procedures.

EDUCATION

Diploma

Aptech Computer Education

2018 - 2021

Courses

Software Engineering

Advanced Level Certification Light College Katikamu

2015 - 2017

Uganda

Uganda

SKILLS

Html Css Postgres Flutter Node.js

React.js Django Adobe XD

LANGUAGES

English
Full Professional Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

Language

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web developer

Andela

09/2018 - 08/2020

Kigali/Rwanda

Andela is an American company with operational campuses in Africa including Nigeria, Rwanda, Ghana & Kenya that identifies and develops software developers.

Contact: Mugerwa Joseph - 0783820477

Freelance
Self employment

2020 - Present

INTERESTS

Research Coding Watching NBA

Watching documentaries Gaming